{
  "task": [
    {
      "question": " Abraham was initially commanded to leave all of the following EXCEPT",
      "time": "12000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. His possessions"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. His country"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. His people "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. His father's household"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. His possessions",
      "type": "epi_8"
    },
    {
      "question": " The great tree of Moreh was in what town? ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Galilee "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Bethel "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Jerusalem "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Shechem "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. Shechem ",
      "type": "epi_8"
    },
    {
      "question": " God first appeared to Abram in the land of Canaan when he was?  ",
      "time": "12000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. By the great tree of Moreh "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. On the threshing floor of Araunah "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c.  By the river Jordan "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. On the mountain of Gilboah "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. By the great tree of Moreh ",
      "type": "epi_8"
    },
    {
      "question": " Why did Abraham go to Egypt?    ",
      "time": "12000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. There was a famine in the land of Canaan "
        },
        {
          "choice": " b. He wanted to trade with the Egyptians "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c.  The Canaanites drove him out "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. He found nowhere to settle among the Canaanites "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " a. There was a famine in the land of Canaan ",
      "type": "epi_8"
    },
    {
      "question": " Where did Abraham build the first altar for God in the land of Canaan? ",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Jerusalem "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Bethel "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Shechem"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Galilee "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. Shechem",
      "type": "epi_8"
    },
    {
      "question": " When the Egyptians saw Sarah's beauty how did they initially respond to Abraham ? ",
      "time": "13000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. They gave Abram the choicest land in Egypt"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. They tried to give him gold and silver "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. They gave him sheep and cattle"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. They blessed Abram's name   "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. They gave him sheep and cattle",
      "type": "epi_8"
    },
    {
      "question": " Between what two towns did Abram build an altar and call upon the name of the Lord? ",
      "time": "12000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Beersheba and Hebron "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b.  Bethel and Ai "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c.  Megiddo and Jezreel "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Jerusalem and Jericho "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "b.  Bethel and Ai ",
      "type": "epi_8"
    },
    {
      "question": " What happened when Pharaoh took Sarah into his palace?",
      "time": "13000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. God caused a famine in the land of Egypt "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. God caused the sun to darken over the land of Egypt "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c.  God inflicted disease on Pharaoh's household "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d.  God rebuked Abram for lying about his wife "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c.  God inflicted disease on Pharaoh's household ",
      "type": "epi_8"
    },
    {
      "question": " When Abraham left Haran, who went with him?  ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Rebekah "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Lot "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c.  His Nephew "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Cousin "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "b. Lot ",
      "type": "epi_8"
    },
    {
      "question": " Why did Abraham says that his wife is his sister in Egypt?  ",
      "time": "15000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. He knew that the Egyptians respected family bonds more than marriage bonds "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. He was afraid they would kill him to get her "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. He feared getting put into prison "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. He was trying to protect her from the Egyptians "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "b. He was afraid they would kill him to get her ",
      "type": "epi_8"
    }
  ]
}